Hello everyone, this is Mathieu from Mint.
Welcome to our beta. While your first project analysis is
being run, and will be displayed in a few minutes,
I recorded this short video to give you a first tour of the platform,
and I will show you how to best use it.
here is your home, where you can see the different projects that you have
and will be creating. The first thing that you can do in terms of
setting up the project and having the right analysis used to go.
And review the project settings.
here you can review the domain name that you are analyzing the
focused market and the main language that would be useful prompt.
and then you can edit and play around with the different.
project parameters, you can work on the competitor set,
you can also expand and improve your visibility from
set along the way by either editing.
In a single prompt,
or by adding new ones. If you want to track new topics,
you can do the same for the alignment analysis.
here the idea is to have the right,
brand attributes or information that will be fact checked in the
different LLM,
answers.
you can add some attributes,
clients are using,
key brands attributes, such as specific information.
That they would like to see displayed in the LLM answers or specific items,
such as pricing,
commission fees, etc., etc.
you can play with the, in defining the right attributes for your brand.
And these are all produced.
But if you want to make adjustment to the fact-checking alignment prompts,
you can also pin it in here.
same for a sentiment. This is a pretty generic and standard analysis.
But if you feel that you want to specify,
some small adjustment to, the sentiment prompts,
you can also edit them here.
last thing on, on the setup part is the account settings.
if you need to adjust your, the plan that you would be using ad
users or select other AI models,
you can do everything here.
that was for the project and account setting parts and now I suggest that
we jump into the analysis and,
join your, your first project.
here you are entering the inside.
The section of the mean platform.
and I will walk you through the different inside that you can gather and
track over time.
based on the setup that we just,
looked at.
the, the first step is to understand and track your
visibility score.
this is the,
percentage of mention that your brand is getting across the
visibility prompt that we have just looked at.
and here you can compare your brand,
against your competitors.
that you have defined, but also the entire industry show voice that
you are getting, including other competitors that you have not mentioned in,
your project setup.
keep in mind that you can,
Always,
check the date and range of the report that you want to look at,
or the model selection as well, if you want to only have a look
to a single model or a setup.
last thing here, once you, you've looked at your visibility score,
that you've tracked it over time, is also to dig into the domain ranking,
looking at the sources that have been consulted by models,
to generate the answers on the visibility answers,
and also check whether this, the sources of belonging to your own assets or
owned by third parties. Second thing is the sentiment of elementers,
the modelers' answers towards your brain.
Here we're tracking with the sentiment prompts whether the answer is coming from
the, whether it's a positive neutral or negative toward your brain.
the idea is to have a look at the overall trend,
whether the sentiment score is positive or not.
And then to dive into the details of getting into the,
the specific,
answers model by model. For example,
here I'm entering one Gemini answer.
what do you think about Lovable? And I can go through the
answer, check the positive items and also keep in mind.
The different weaknesses or limitations that the models are pointing out to users
that would be researching your brand.
you can get into the details and also have a look at the intermediate
queries that can be formulated by models.
All the citations, the websites that are being used.
To make the answer.
likewise, you can go deeper into the analysis by looking at all the sources
that have been consulted by models that you can filter out by either the
kind of models and the sentiment.
If you want to look at a specific category,
and what we truly believe is that the real value lies into the,
into the details,
Next up is alignment.
here we're looking at,
reinforcing your brand protection,
and compliance across the model's answer.
you can track your overall alignment score.
That would be deep. The average of all the model's answer across all attributes.
here, again, the idea is to make sure that the,
present representation and that the,
characteristic that you're- would like to see displayed to users using
AI search or being,
being displayed correctly.
you can have a look at any attributes,
treated by any model and- and do the same good- into the details
of- of understanding what is the answer,
what are the intermediate queries,
what are the citations, the website that have been consulting to,
to build the- the answer. Similarly,
you can go into the- sources details to make sure that you,
for example, have a look at the sources that would be misaligned with the
brand that's enriched that you want to understand.
For instance, here, the team at Lovable would be interested in understanding why the,
for example, here, the rapid developer. This source is not aligning with the messages
that I want to, that I want to see this play. Last insight,
analysis that we are offering to you is the competitive
landscape analysis,
here we are comparing you. Your brand versus the selected competitors,
where you can see if,
the prospect of the client is researching your brand,
your brand against another one, what would be the strength and the weaknesses
that would be displayed in the answers.
for all the other sections, you can also go into the sources and understand
what are the,
exact sources that are being consulted and where you could have,
potentially influence,
going forward. The last,
and the last interesting section is the Data Explorer.
Here the idea is that you have the full database of all the links
that I've been consulting throughout the different prompts,
throughout the different models, and to build the first report.
and here the idea is that you can,
feature out this database by the internet queries that are being used
in the indexes.
you can have a focus on sources, on model,
on prompt. If I want to have a look on the visibility,
the organic one, if I want to understand if Wikipedia is being used or,
Reddit is being also talked about.
you can play around with the database and understand,
what were the factors of, of in-prem. For every answer,
and you can also export it to CSV to make sure that you really
go deeper into the analysis and start optimizing by,
potentially influencing,
some of your content, for instance,
on your own domain, but also third-party contents once you- have,
identify it.
this is it for now,
the first quick tour of all the inside picture that we've
been for you so far. I'm looking forward to hearing from you
using the beta, getting your- feedback, and hopefully you will enjoy
using mint as much as we do. Thank you very much.
See you soon.